FACUNDO ARAGON

Full Stack Web Developer

Email: <u>facundo_aragon@hotmail.com</u>

LinkedIn: <u>Facundo Aragon</u>
GitHub: <u>facuaragon</u>

Location: Buenos Aires, Argentina

Phone: +54 9 11 6641 4910

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Web Design. Experience working with React, Redux, NodeJs, Express, SQL, and other technologies in the sector. Currently, I am in continuous learning, developing personal projects to reinforce what I have learned and expand my knowledge. I am a sociable and proactive person who works well in a team, embraces challenges, and excels at problem-solving. I have acquired these skills during my previous work experience in the construction industry, where I physically carried out tasks on-site. As a Construction Manager, I successfully completed projects within agreed timelines and budgets. I led teams of architects and administrative staff, as well as on-site personnel and subcontractors for the execution of all tasks.

PROYECTOS

Jun-2023 Full Stack Web Developer - Consumedic

Academic Experience - Henry Bootcamp - Final Group Project

Designed and developed an App that allows users to book appointments with healthcare professionals, including third-party authentication, Mercado Pago integration, Cloudinary integration, Admin panel, Medical and Patient profile panels, mailing functionality, local storage, and logical deletion.

Specifically, some of the tasks I was responsable for included:

- Creating database models, defining their relationships, and designing the server request routes with their respective logic for data retrieval.
- Developing the agenda component for each doctor, both in the Backend and Frontend.
- Building the Medical profile panel, where information about patients, their medical history, appointments, and the ability to send messages and upload files was displayed.
- And more

Tecnologías Utilizadas:

- Frontend: JS, React, Context, Material-UI
- Backend: NodeJS, Express
- Extras: Nodemailer, Cloudinary, Mercado Pago, Google Login
- Database: PostgreSQL, Sequelize

Repository: <u>PF-soyHenry</u> Deployed Link: <u>Consumedic</u>

May-2023 Full Stack Web Developer - Dogs PI

Academic Experience - Henry Bootcamp - Individual Project

Designed and developed a Dog Breeds App that included searches, combined filters, sorting, as well as a form for creating new breeds.

Tecnologías Utilizadas:

• Frontend: JS, HTML, CSS, React, Redux

Backend: NodeJS, Express

Database: PostgreSQL, Sequelize

Deployed Link: PI-Dogs

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 Novadomus S.R.L.

Construction Manager

Project: Directorio 223, Caballito, CABA 13-story building with 2 basements

Constructed Area: 7.006m2

- Leadership and management of the assigned project team.
- Planning and project monitoring.
- Efficient coordination and administration of all company resources allocated to the specific project.
- Monitoring and supervision of quantity surveying management.
- Analysis and planning for the upcoming Carlos Calvo 3660 project.
- Implementation of work procedures to improve operational efficiency and productivity.
- Problem-solving related to construction issues, with responsibility for construction finishing details.

2019-2021 OBRAS Y SISTEMAS S.R.L.

Construction Manager

Project: University Institute - Anesthesia, Analgesia and Resucitation Association of Buenos Aires - Aranguren 1337, Caballito, CABA.

2-story building with 2 basements

Constructed Area: 4.315,21m²

- Team leader for the construction project.
- Formation of the construction team.
- Management of documentation for project initiation.
- Coordination of the executive project.
- Preparation of Work Certificates.
- Coordination of human and material resources.
- Supervision, update, coordination, and control of execution programs.
- Administrative and economic control during the construction period.
- Supervision and inspection of construction stages.

2015-2018 OBRAS Y SISTEMAS S.R.L.

Assistant Construction Manager

Project: Office Building and Parking Lot - Av. de Mayo 1145, Monserrat, CABA.

12-story building with 6 basements

Constructed Area: 9.093,00m²

- Coordination of the executive project.
- Preparation of Work Certificates.
- Supervision, update, coordination, and control of execution programs.
- Administrative and economic control during the construction period.

- Negotiation with subcontractors and control of their tasks and progress certificates.
- Preparation of material purchase orders.
- Concrete programming and logistics in material delivery.
- Supervision and inspection of construction stages, special tests, and assemblies.
- Verification of submitted documentation.
- Preparation and continuous update of communication books.

2014-2015 OBRAS Y SISTEMAS S.R.L.

Supervisor

Project: Grand View - Av. Rivadavia 2355, Balvanera, CABA.

27-story tower building with 3 basements

Constructed Area: 28.274,89m²

- Supervision and inspection of construction stages.
- Formwork and reinforcement control.
- Verification of submitted documentation.
- Preparation and continuous update of communication books
- Follow-up of purchase orders, subcontracting, and provision control.
- Quantity surveying and budgeting.

2014 OBRAS Y SISTEMAS S.R.L.

Technical Office - Bidding Department

- Participation in the bidding process.
- Quantity surveying and budgeting.
- Cost analysis and price comparisons.

2011-2012 Agua y Saneamientos Argentinos S.A.

Young Professionals Contract - Planning Department

- Preparation of tender documents.
- Special involvement in the ACUBA Industrial Collector project (Wilde)

EDUCATION

2023 Soy Henry

6 month Fullstack Developer Bootcamp

2008- 2013 CATHOLIC ARGENTINE UNIVERSITY

Civil Engineering Final Project pending

2007 CHAMPAGNAT SCHOOL

Bachelor's Degree with focus on Economics

Languages

• English:

Excellent oral and written proficiency.

- o Certificate: EF Standard English Test 74/100 C2 Proficient
- Exams: 2018 International English Testing System (IELTS), 2004 First Certificate in English (FCE)

RECREATIONAL ACTIVITIES

1996-2017 Rugby, Champagnat Club. Member of the First Team since 2009.